shnsf.com 2012-03-26

# SHN: Broadway theatre, shows & events in San Francisco - Privacy Policy - Official Ticket Site of Broadway in San Francisco

SHN Online Privacy Statement

At SHN we are committed to respecting your privacy. Our website is structured so that, in general, you can visit our website and obtain information without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. If you opt to provide us with personally identifiable information -- any information by which you can be identified – this information will only be used to enhance and support your customer relationship with SHN. 

We provide this Online Privacy Statement to advise you of our privacy policy and practices and make you aware of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**What Information is Collected**  
On some of the web pages within our website you are given the opportunity to register with us and, as a result of that registration, to receive information and materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may be such items as your name, email address and other contact information. In order to tailor our subsequent communications to you and continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our services, and contact preferences. This information is provided to us voluntarily by you. 

**How We Use Information Collected Through Our Website**  
SHN uses the information you provide us to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Specifically, we use your information to communicate back to you, to update you on services and benefits, and to personalize and enhance our web site and our communications for you. At any time you will have the opportunity to opt out of receiving information from us based on the personally identifying information you have provided. 

**We Do Not Share Personally Identifiable Information With Others**  
SHN will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other member entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf to complete the activities described above. Such member entities and/or business partners, including those located in other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data. 

SHN will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first advising you and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive tailored or enhanced information from us based upon the personally identifiable information you have provided to us. We will do everything we can to honor such requests. 

**Security**  
SHN is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**SHN Website Privacy Officer**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our website, or your dealings with our website, you can contact our SHN Website [Privacy Officer](mailto:privacyofficer@shnsf.com).

 **Copyright ©2005 SHN All rights reserved. ******

 ** ******

**** ****
